<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Franziska Menti</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Franziska Menti</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;To make sure everything works as expected and looks pretty, on this page, we will explore how different types of content are displayed by this theme.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="headings"&gt;Headings&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The following HTML &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;—&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;h6&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; elements represent six levels of section headings. &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; is the highest section level while &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;h6&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; is the lowest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id="h1"&gt;H1&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id="h2"&gt;H2&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id="h3"&gt;H3&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id="h4"&gt;H4&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h5 id="h5"&gt;H5&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;h6 id="h6"&gt;H6&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h2 id="paragraph"&gt;Paragraph&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id="just-a-normal-paragraph"&gt;Just a normal paragraph&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Xerum, quo qui aut unt expliquam qui dolut labo. Aque venitatiusda cum, voluptionse latur sitiae dolessi aut parist aut dollo enim qui voluptate ma dolestendit peritin re plis aut quas inctum laceat est volestemque commosa as cus endigna tectur, offic to cor sequas etum rerum idem sintibus eiur? Quianimin porecus evelectur, cum que nis nust voloribus ratem aut omnimi, sitatur?&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Autism</title><link>/autism/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/autism/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="what-is-autism"&gt;What is Autism?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I like the definition of &lt;a href="https://reframingautism.org.au/about-autism/"&gt;Refrainingautism&lt;/a&gt; very well:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;We think of Autism as a brain difference that is basic and fundamental to who we are. This means that Autism is an important part of who we are and the way we are in the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Autistic people develop differently to non-autistic people. Autistic people think, move, interact, sense and process differently to what people might expect. We also have more qualities and characteristics in common with other Autistic people than with non-autistic people. Each person is different, but Autistic people will be different to non-autistic people in the way we:&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Hobbies</title><link>/hobbies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hobbies/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I love training animals (especially my cat and my dog), reading fantasy or scify books (especially those from Brandon Sanderson and Michael Sullivan) and playing games (D&amp;amp;D / Pathfinder, tabletop games, computer games,&amp;hellip;).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On my daily cat walks I often get asked, how one teaches a cat to walk on a leash or why I even do it. Those and many more questions I address in the next section.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure&gt;
 &lt;img src="/highfive0.jpg" widt="300" height="300" /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;h2 id="cat_training_guide"&gt;Cat Training Guide&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id="introduction"&gt;Introduction&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s first cover the four most important questions about what this guide is about:&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Privacy policy</title><link>/privacy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/privacy/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This is where the imprint should go.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Publications</title><link>/publications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/publications/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="science"&gt;Science&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Menti F. et al: The LIFE Target Star Database LIFETD, TAP-published
table set, doi:&lt;a href="https://dc.zah.uni-heidelberg.de/voidoi/q/lp/custom/10.21938/ke_e6lzO_jjX_vzvVIcwZA"&gt;10.21938/ke_e6lzO_jjX_vzvVIcwZA&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Menti F. et al: Database of Candidate Targets for the LIFE Mission
(&lt;a href="https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2024RNAAS...8..267M/abstract"&gt;NASA/ADS&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="https://arxiv.org/abs/2410.23892"&gt;arxiv&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Menti F.: Franziska Menti - LIFE target data base update, &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VqYf2tvb5OQ"&gt;youtube video&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h1 id="pub_employment"&gt;Employment&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After finishing my master at ETH Zurich I am now employed through &lt;a href="https://workaut.ch/"&gt;Workaut&lt;/a&gt; which offers a program for inclusion of autistic people in workplaces. You can read more about it in the article of the ETH community magazine that featured me:&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>