<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Franziska Menti</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Franziska Menti</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Another post, this time with LaTeX</title><link>/posts/2021/09/01/another-post/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/2021/09/01/another-post/</guid><description>This is another dummy blog post in which we also use LaTeX. Since the Pythagorean theorem is slightly overused as an example, how about we go with the time-dependent Schrödinger equation instead?
$$ i\hbar {\frac {d}{dt}}\vert \Psi (t)\rangle ={\hat {H}}\vert \Psi (t)\rangle $$
See? It works beautifully! We can even use LaTeX inline to explain that $\Psi$ is the state vector of the quantum system, and $\hat{H}$ is the Hamiltonian.</description></item><item><title>My first post (with an image)</title><link>/posts/2021/08/31/first-post/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/2021/08/31/first-post/</guid><description>Sometimes, blog posts (or normal pages) will also contain an image, this is why we provide an example here to test the stylesheets for this.
Wikipedia says: "Monte Altissimo di Nago is one of the highest summits of the Monte Baldo mountain range and thereby part of the Garda Mountains in northern Italy." Source: Unsplash. Looks pretty good, I&amp;rsquo;d say? If we just continue this text for a little longer, we can probably also test how / if the summary feature works, and where the truncation occurs.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>To make sure everything works as expected and looks pretty, on this page, we will explore how different types of content are displayed by this theme.
Headings The following HTML &amp;lt;h1&amp;gt;—&amp;lt;h6&amp;gt; elements represent six levels of section headings. &amp;lt;h1&amp;gt; is the highest section level while &amp;lt;h6&amp;gt; is the lowest.
H1 H2 H3 H4 H5 H6 Paragraph Just a normal paragraph Xerum, quo qui aut unt expliquam qui dolut labo. Aque venitatiusda cum, voluptionse latur sitiae dolessi aut parist aut dollo enim qui voluptate ma dolestendit peritin re plis aut quas inctum laceat est volestemque commosa as cus endigna tectur, offic to cor sequas etum rerum idem sintibus eiur?</description></item><item><title>Autism</title><link>/autism/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/autism/</guid><description>Sorry, I am still working on getting the content here ready.
I am autistic.
What is Autism?
As described by https://reframingautism.org.au/about-autism/: &amp;ldquo;At Reframing Autism, we think of Autism as a brain difference that is basic and fundamental to who we are. This means that Autism is an important part of who we are and the way we are in the world.
Autistic people develop differently to non-autistic people. Autistic people think, move, interact, sense and process differently to what people might expect.</description></item><item><title>Employment</title><link>/employment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/employment/</guid><description>After finishing my master at ETH Zurich I am now employed through Workaut (https://workaut.ch/) which offers a program for inclusion of autistic people in workplaces. You can read more about it in the article of the ETH community magazine that featured me:
Anna Maltsev, &amp;ldquo;A rush of senses&amp;rdquo;, life, October 2022, page 10. (https://ethz.ch/content/dam/ethz/associates/services/News/life/ausgaben/englisch/ETH-Life-Oktober-EN_ACC.pdf)</description></item><item><title>Hobbies</title><link>/hobbies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/hobbies/</guid><description>My Hobbies I love training animals (especially my cat and my dog), reading fantasy or scify books (especially those from Brandon Sanderson and Michael Sullivan) and playing games (D&amp;amp;D / Pathfinder, tabletop games, computer games,&amp;hellip;).
On my daily cat walks I often get asked, how one teaches a cat to walk on a leash or why I even do it. Those and many more questions I address in the next section.</description></item><item><title>Privacy policy</title><link>/privacy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/privacy/</guid><description>This is where the imprint should go.</description></item><item><title>Publications</title><link>/publications/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/publications/</guid><description>Science Menti F. et al: The LIFE Target Star Database LIFETD, TAP-published table set, doi:10.21938/ke_e6lzO_jjX_vzvVIcwZA Employment After finishing my master at ETH Zurich I am now employed through Workaut which offers a program for inclusion of autistic people in workplaces. You can read more about it in the article of the ETH community magazine that featured me:
Anna Maltsev, &amp;ldquo;A rush of senses&amp;rdquo;, life, October 2022, page 10.</description></item></channel></rss>